#### Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/nt0412 (LinkedIn) namthuan0412.framer.website (Portfolio) www.tiktok.com/@namthuan0412 (Personal)

## Top Skills

Mobile User Interface Design Framer Self-Management

## Languages

Vietnamese (Native or Bilingual) English (Professional Working)

### Certifications

SKILLS FOR FUTURE
PRODUCT OWNER
PROFESSIONAL CERTIFICATION

Ambassador at Product Management Essentials 2024

Foundations of User Experience (UX) Design

Runner-up at Lollypop Designathon 2024

# Thuan Nguyen

UX/UI Designer at VieON | Mentor at MindX | Video Content Creator at Pint of Design | Figma/Framer Lover | Top 2 at Lollypop Designathon 2024

Ho Chi Minh City, Vietnam

# Summary

I am Thuan - a UX/UI Designer with almost 3 years of experience, working closely with Clients, PO/PMs, and Developers, participating in projects and products for both B2B and B2C sectors related to Blockchain, Web3, NFTs, AI, and Hospitality,... This involves catering to various mobile, desktop, tablet, and TV devices. In addition to my work, I enjoy sharing my knowledge about Design Patterns, UX Laws, Design Systems, and Figma tips through my TikTok channel, to inspire others.

https://namthuan0412.framer.website/

## Experience

VieON UX/UI Designer July 2024 - Present (9 months) Ho Chi Minh City, Vietnam

Pint of Design - Vietnam UX/UI, Product and Creative Design Community

UX/UI Video Content Creator October 2024 - Present (6 months)

Ho Chi Minh City, Vietnam

Vietnam UX-UI & Creative Design Community

Help designers to strive for a better future!

Join us at "Pint of Design" to be part of this exciting journey towards a more creative and connected future.

https://www.facebook.com/pintofdesign

MindX Technology School UX/UI Teaching Mentor August 2024 - Present (8 months) Ho Chi Minh City, Vietnam Moonscape
UX/UI Designer
May 2024 - July 2024 (3 months)
England, United Kingdom

Hash Consulting Group (HCG)
UX/UI Designer
March 2023 - April 2024 (1 year 2 months)
Ho Chi Minh City, Vietnam

All projects and products at HCG are under NDA, preventing me from publicly sharing my work during my time here.

Beowulf Blockchain UX/UI Designer July 2022 - March 2023 (9 months) District 1, Ho Chi Minh City, Vietnam

Dolphin Technology UX Designer, Front-end Developer August 2021 - June 2022 (11 months) Ho Chi Minh City, Vietnam

## Education

Ton Duc Thang University
Bachelor's degree, Information Technology · (2019 - 2022)